Narrator: 1
Interviewer: Did you like school?
S1: I didn’t hate school, but I don’t think I liked it very much.
I used to enjoy PE, I used to enjoy sport, um, I quite liked English, but there were lots of subjects I didn’t like.
I didn’t like maths very much, history was boring, and I found science difficult.
I had a small group of friends – not many, but a close group of friends –
and I used to spend time with them talking about sport, talking about music.
So it wasn’t too bad, but I didn’t like it very much.
I’ve never been back to school – I’ve never been to a school reunion, or anything like that.
Narrator: 2
Interviewer: Did you like school?
S2: No, not really.
I didn’t like it at all.
Interviewer: Why not?
S2: It was a boys’ school and I got bored with just being with boys all the time.
And I didn’t really like any of the subjects.
Narrator: 3
Interviewer: Did you like school?
S3: Well, yes and no.
Some things I really loved, some things I thought, ‘this isn’t much fun’,
but I used to enjoy quite a lot of the subjects.
Interviewer: Like what?
S3: I liked English and I liked maths.
Interviewer: And what didn’t you enjoy?
S3: I hated geography.
And I hated PE.
The PE teacher once caught me reading a book on the football pitch, and I was punished for that.
Narrator: 4
Interviewer: Did you like school?
S4: I didn’t like it – I absolutely loved it! I liked all the subjects, especially English and history.
I remember one time when I was about six or seven, I got ill during the Easter holidays and I was really, really sad,
and my mum thought I was sad because I was ill during the holidays,
but in fact I was terrified that I’d never get better and I’d never go back to school.
Narrator: 5
Interviewer: Did you like school?
S5: Er, sometimes.
Yeah, most of the time.
Interviewer: What did you like about it?
S5: Well, I had some good friends, and I liked learning things,
but there were some subjects that I didn’t like very much and I hated PE.
I used to invent a lot of excuses, like saying that I was ill, because I didn’t want to do it.
Narrator: 6
Interviewer: Did you like school?
S6: Yes, overall, I really enjoyed school, though there were some things I didn’t like.
Interviewer: Like what?
S6: In English I found reading long texts very hard, as I have dyslexia,
and because of this my handwriting was also slow and messy.
And I struggle with numbers too, so maths and physics were very difficult for me.
Interviewer: What things did you like?
S6: Um, I discovered I was interested in history,
because my teachers were passionate about what they taught, which made me want to learn.
But I enjoyed visual and active learning much more,
so subjects like drama, art and cooking were some of my favourites.